Guide to the Carnegie Endowment for International Peace pamphlet and microfilm collection, 1817-1950 MS2110
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Unbound pamphlets, 1817-1950; MS2110 Series 2; 47 Linear feet
  - "China's Stand on Sino-Japanese Economic Co-operation", 1940 (Box 14, Folder 60)
    Subject: China; Previous folder number: F-3-31, Author:China Institute of International Affairs; vol 2. no. 3
  - "The Nature of Sino-Japanese Peace Talks", 1940 (Box 14, Folder 61)
    Subject: China; Previous folder number: F-3-32, Author:China Institute of International Affairs; vol. 2 no. 6
  - "Peace Movement in Japan", 1940 (Box 14, Folder 62)
    Subject: China; Previous folder number: F-3-33, Author:China Institute of International Affairs; vol. 2 no. 4
  - "The Reorganization of the Central Government of China", 1940 (Box 14, Folder 63)
    Subject: China; Previous folder number: F-3-34, Author:China Institute of International Affairs; vol. 2 no. 1
  - "Third Powers Interests in China", 1940 (Box 14, Folder 64)
    Subject: China; Previous folder number: F-3-35, Author:China Institute of International Affairs; vol. 2 no. 5
  - "China Charges Russia of Obstructing Reestablishment of Chinese Authority of Dairen and Port Arthur", 1947 (Box 14, Folder 65)
    Subject: China; Previous folder number: F-3-36, Author:Chinese Ministry of Foreign Affairs
  - "Contemporary China: The Food Situation in China", 1943 (Box 14, Folder 66)
    Subject: China; Previous folder number: F-3-37, Author:Chinese News Service
  - "A Message Addressed to the People of Friendly Nations", 1940 (Box 14, Folder 67)
    Subject: China; Previous folder number: F-3-38, Author:Chu, Chia-Hua
  - "I Speak for the Chinese", 1938 (Box 14, Folder 68)
    Subject: China; Previous folder number: F-3-39, Author:Crow, Carl; China Reference Series
  - "League of Nations Reports", 1937 (Box 14, Folder 69)
    Subject: China; Previous folder number: F-3-40, Author:China Reference Series
  - "A Bird's Eye View of European Sinology", 1931 (Box 14, Folder 70)
    Subject: China; Previous folder number: F-3-41, Author:Duyvencale, J.J.L.
  - "Overseas Chinese Rally to Aid of Fatherland", 1938 (Box 14, Folder 71)
    Subject: China; Previous folder number: F-3-42, Author:Federation of Chinese Cultural Associations
  - "Films from China", 1938 ca. (Box 14, Folder 72)
    Subject: China; Previous folder number: F-3-43
  - "Is the Peace Machinery Imperiled by the Far East Situation?", 1932 (Box 14, Folder 73)
    Subject: China; Previous folder number: F-3-44, Author:Foreign Policy Association
  - "Manchuria", 1932 (Box 14, Folder 74)
    Subject: China; Previous folder number: F-3-45, Author:Foreign Policy Association
  - "The United States and the Situation in the Far East", 1932 ca. (Box 14, Folder 75)
    Subject: China; Previous folder number: F-3-46, Author:Greene, Jerome Davis
  - "China Fights Civilization's Battle", 1938 (Box 14, Folder 76)
    Subject: China; Previous folder number: F-3-47, Author:Gilbert, Rodney
  - "Freedom: Manchuria's Plea for Independence", 1935 ca. (Box 14, Folder 77)
    Subject: China; Previous folder number: F-3-48, Author:Gorman, George
  - "In the Far East", 1933 (Box 14, Folder 78)
    Subject: China; Previous folder number: F-3-49, Author:Herriot, Edouard
  - "International Law and the Undeclared War", 1937 (Box 14, Folder 79)
    Subject: China; Previous folder number: F-3-50, Author:Hsitieu, Mousheng
  - "Nationalist China", 1929 (Box 14, Folder 80)
    Subject: China; Previous folder number: F-3-51, Author:Hung, William
  - "China's Resistance", 1938 (Box 14, Folder 81)
    Subject: China; Previous folder number: F-3-52, Author:International Affairs Watchers
  - "Directors Report", 1912 (Box 14, Folder 82)
    Subject: China; Previous folder number: F-3-53, Author:International Institute of China
  - "Endorsements of the International Institute", 1921 ca. (Box 14, Folder 83)
    Subject: China; Previous folder number: F-3-54, Author:International Institute of China
  - "International Institute of China", n.d. (Box 14, Folder 84)
    Subject: China; Previous folder number: F-3-55, Author:International Institute of China
  - "Letter", 1912 (Box 14, Folder 85)
    Subject: China; Previous folder number: F-3-56, Author:International Institute of China
  - "A Prospectus of the International Institute of China", 1910 ca. (Box 14, Folder 86)
    Subject: China; Previous folder number: F-3-57, Author:International Institute of China
  - "Joint Manifesto of Chinese and Korean Students in Greater New York (N.Y.) on Manchurian Dispute", 1932 ca. (Box 14, Folder 87)
    Subject: China; Previous folder number: F-3-58
  - "China and the Problem of Narcotics Before the League of Nations", 1929 (Box 14, Folder 88)
    Subject: China; Previous folder number: F-3-59, Author:Ky, Wang King
  - "China and the Discovery of America", 1931 (Box 14, Folder 89)
    Subject: China; Previous folder number: F-3-60, Author:Laufer, Berthold
  - "Appeals to the Commission of the Inquiry of the League of Nations by the Chinese Alumni of Imperial Universities of Japan", 1932 ca. (Box 14, Folder 90)
    Subject: China; Previous folder number: F-3-61, Author:League of Nations
  - "The Far Eastern Crisis", 1933 (Box 14, Folder 91)
    Subject: China; Previous folder number: F-3-62, Author:League of Nations
  - "The League Manchuria, and Disarmament", 1931 (Box 14, Folder 92)
    Subject: China; Previous folder number: F-3-63, Author:League of Nations Union
  - "Let the Civilized World Judge", 1938 ca. (Box 14, Folder 93)
    Subject: China; Previous folder number: F-3-64
  - "The First Year of the Far Eastern Crisis", 1932 (Box 14, Folder 94)
    Subject: China; Previous folder number: F-3-65, Author:Liang, Yun-li
  - "Petition Initiated February 17th 1932, Concerning the American Attitude During the Shanghai Crisis", 1932 ca. (Box 14, Folder 95)
    Subject: China; Previous folder number: F-3-66, Author:Lowell, Abbot Lawrence
  - "The Lytton Report - And After", 1935 (Box 14, Folder 96)
    Subject: China; Previous folder number: F-3-66, Author:bLytton, Victor
  - Manchuria Pamphlets, 1931-1934 (Box 14, Folder 97)
    Subject: China; Previous folder number: F-3-67
  - "At Home and at the Front", 1933 (Box 14, Folder 98)
    Subject: China; Previous folder number: F-3-68, Author:Martin, William
  - "China Will Win", 1941 ca. (Box 14, Folder 99)
    Subject: China; Previous folder number: F-3-69, Author:McNutt, Paul V.
  - "The Ordinance for the General Regulation of Traders of the Chinese Republic", 1914 ca. (Box 14, Folder 100)
    Subject: China; Previous folder number: F-3-70
  - "Deadlock in China", 1940 (Box 14, Folder 101)
    Subject: China; Previous folder number: F-3-71, Author:Rosinger, Lawrence K.
  - "Manchuria and the Lytton Report", 1937 ca. (Box 14, Folder 102)
    Subject: China; Previous folder number: F-3-74, Author:Saito, Hirosi
  - "Shanghai's Refugee Problem", 1937 ca. (Box 14, Folder 103)
    Subject: China; Previous folder number: F-3-75, Author:Shanghai Citizen's League
  - "The China Incident and Manchuria", 1937 ca. (Box 14, Folder 104)
    Subject: China; Previous folder number: F-3-76, Author:South Manchuria Railway Company Information and Publicity Department
  - "Non-Participation in Aggression as a National Policy", 1938 (Box 14, Folder 105)
    Subject: China; Previous folder number: F-3-77, Author:Tsune-Chi Yu
  - "The Great Teachers Lectures", 1937 ca. (Box 14, Folder 106)
    Subject: China; Previous folder number: F-3-78, Author:Tuan Szetsun
  - "United Council for Civilian Relief in China", 1938 ca. (Box 14, Folder 107)
    Subject: China; Previous folder number: F-3-79
  - "China Presents Her Case to the United Nations", 1949 (Box 14, Folder 108)
    Subject: China; Previous folder number: F-3-80, Author:United Nations General Assembly
  - "Character Building Citizenship Training International Good Will", 1927 ca. (Box 14, Folder 109)
    Subject: China; Previous folder number: F-3-81, Author:Young Men's Christian Association of China
  - "Extraterritoriality in China", 1931 (Box 14, Folder 110)
    Subject: China; Previous folder number: F-3-82, Author:Wang, China-Chun
  - "Law Reform in China", 1919 (Box 14, Folder 111)
    Subject: China; Previous folder number: F-3-83, Author:Wang, Chung-Hui
  - "The Local Government of China", 1945 (Box 14, Folder 112)
    Subject: China; Previous folder number: F-3-84, Author:Wang, Kan-Yu
  - "International Co-operation and Organization of National", 1937 (Box 14, Folder 113)
    Subject: China; Previous folder number: F-3-85, Author:Wei, Wang Ching
  - "The Conflict of Policies In China", 1925 (Box 14, Folder 114)
    Subject: China; Previous folder number: F-3-86, Author:Wen Kuo, Ping
  - "The Founder of Polish Independence - Joseph Pilsudski", 1921 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    Subject: Eastern Europe; Previous folder number: F-4a-1, Author:Boncza, St. J.
  - "The German-Polish Rye Agreement", 1931 ca. (Box 15, Folder 2)
    Subject: Eastern Europe; Previous folder number: F-4a-2, Author:Colegrove, Kenneth
  - "The Strength of the National Consciousness of the Albanian People", 1918 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    Subject: Eastern Europe; Previous folder number: F-4a-3, Author:Dako, Chirsto Anastos
  - "Polish Russian Relations - Past and Present", 1943 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Subject: Eastern Europe; Previous folder number: F-4a-4, Author:Halecki, Oscar
  - "An Albanian Letter", 1940 ca. (Box 15, Folder 5)
    Subject: Eastern Europe; Previous folder number: F-4a-5, Author:Italian Library of Information
  - "Poland, Russia, and Great Britain", 1943 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    Subject: Eastern Europe; Previous folder number: F-4a-6, Author:Nineteenth Century and After, The
  - "The Hell of Brest-Litowsk Before the Polish Sejm", 1931 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    Subject: Eastern Europe; Previous folder number: F-4a-6, Author:bPilsudski, Marshal
  - "History of Pacifism in Poland", 1930 ca. (Box 15, Folder 8)
    Subject: Eastern Europe; Previous folder number: F-4a-7, Author:Polak, J.
  - "Documents & Reports on Poland", 1948 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    Subject: Eastern Europe; Previous folder number: F-4a-8, Author:Polish Information Center
  - "Life in Contemporary Poland", 1941 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    Subject: Eastern Europe; Previous folder number: F-4a-9, Author:Polish Information Center
  - "Points Concerning Eastern Poland", 1944 ca. (Box 15, Folder 11)
    Subject: Eastern Europe; Previous folder number: F-4a-10, Author:Polish Information Center
  - Minc, Hilary"Poland's Economy: Present & Future", 1949 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    Subject: Eastern Europe; Previous folder number: F-4a-11, Author:Polish Information Center
  - [Polish-Soviet Relations], 1945 ca. (Box 15, Folder 13)
    Subject: Eastern Europe; Previous folder number: F-4a-12
  - "Polish-Soviet Relations: 1918-1943" (Box 15, Folder 14)
    Subject: Eastern Europe; Previous folder number: F-4a-13, Author:Polish Information Center
  - "The Polish Constitution of the Third of May" Poland's National Holiday, 1943 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    Subject: Eastern Europe; Previous folder number: F-4a-14, Author:Polish Information Center
  - "Workmen's Protective Legislation in Poland", 1940 ca. (Box 15, Folder 16)
    Subject: Eastern Europe; Previous folder number: F-4a-15, Author:Stanczyk, Jan
  - "American Support of Free Institutions in Eastern Europe", 1948 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    Subject: Eastern Europe; Previous folder number: F-4a-16, Author:Yale Institute of International Studies
  - "The Influence of Grenville on Pitt's Foreign Policy", 1904 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    Subject European History; Previous folder number: F-4b-1, Author:Adams, Ephraim Douglas
  - "The Story of the British Commonwealth and Empire", 1947 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    Subject European History; Previous folder number: F-4b-2, Author:British Information Service
  - "The Last Resting Place of Columbus", 1928 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    Subject European History; Previous folder number: F-4b-3, Author:Cronau, Rudolf
  - "Karl Marx, Friedreich Engels, and the South Slavic Problem in 1848-1849", 1939 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    Subject European History; Previous folder number: F-4b-4, Author:MacDonald, H. Malcolm
  - "The Slavs Among the Nations", 1916 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    Subject European History; Previous folder number: F-4b-5, Author:Masaryk, J.G.
  - "German Aggression on France and French Aggression against Germany During the Last 1000 Years", 1923 ca. (Box 15, Folder 23)
    Subject European History; Previous folder number: F-4b-6, Author:Mendelssohn - Bartholdy, A.
  - "Beust's Appointment as Austrian Foreign Minister", 1943 ca. (Box 15, Folder 24)
    Subject European History; Previous folder number: F-4b-7, Author:Prange, Gordon W.
  - "The European Quandary", 1931 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    Subject European History; Previous folder number: F-4b-8, Author:Simonds, Frank H; Foreign Policy Association, no. 77
  - "The State in Its External Relations", 1932 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    Subject European History; Previous folder number: F-4b-9, Author:Temple, William
  - "Requisition During the French Revolution (1789-1815)", 1944 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    Subject European History; Previous folder number: F-4b-10, Author:Wise, Maurice K.
  - "The Prime Minister of Great Britain Speaks on Anglo-American Relations", 1929 ca. (Box 15, Folder 28)
    Subject Western Europe; Previous folder number: F-4c-1, Author:Baldwin, Stanley
  - "France and the Pope", 1907 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    Subject Western Europe; Previous folder number: F-4c-2, Author:Birney, General William
  - "Switzerland and the Zone Controversy with France", 1931 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    Subject Western Europe; Previous folder number: F-4c-3, Author:Blake, Gilson G.
  - "History of the Peace Movement in the Netherlands", 1920 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    Subject Western Europe; Previous folder number: F-4c-4, Author:En Donk, Jon Van Beek
  - "The Aland Question and the Rights of Finland", 1920 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    Subject Western Europe; Previous folder number: F-4c-5, Author:Finnish Jurists and Historians
  - "England Seeks a Way Out", 1932 (Box 15, Folder 33)
    Subject Western Europe; Previous folder number: F-4c-6, Author:Foreign Policy Association
  - "British Public Opinion Kills the Anglo-French Naval Agreement and Demands Understanding with America", 1928 (Box 15, Folder 34)
    Subject Western Europe; Previous folder number: F-4c-7, Author:Martin, John
  - "Declaration of the Bohemian (Czech) Foreign Committee", 1915 (Box 15, Folder 35)
    Subject Western Europe; Previous folder number: F-4c-8, Author:Masaryk, Professor T.G.
  - "Peace and Permanent Recovery", 1937 (Box 15, Folder 36)
    Subject Western Europe; Previous folder number: F-4c-9, Author:Paish, George, Sir
  - "The Political Rights of Women in the Czechoslovak Republic", 1920 (Box 15, Folder 37)
    Subject Western Europe; Previous folder number: F-4c-10, Author:Plaminkova, F.
  - "Agrarian Problems from the Baltic to the Aegean", 1944 (Box 15, Folder 38)
    Subject Western Europe; Previous folder number: F-4c-11, Author:Royal Institute of International Affairs
  - "German Socialists and Belgium", 1919 ca. (Box 15, Folder 39)
    Subject Western Europe; Previous folder number: F-4c-12, Author:Royer, Emile
  - "The Position of Aland in Historical Times" (Finland), 1919 (Box 15, Folder 40)
    Subject Western Europe; Previous folder number: F-4c-13, Author:Schybergson, M.G.
  - "Post-War Government of the Netherlands East Indies", 1947 (Box 15, Folder 41)
    Subject Western Europe; Previous folder number: F-4c-14, Author:Steiner, H. Arthur
  - "Austria: 1918-1938" (Box 15, Folder 42)
    Subject Western Europe; Previous folder number: F-4c-15, Author:Union of Democratic Control, The
  - "Formulation and Control of Foreign Policy in the Netherlands", 1944 (Box 15, Folder 43)
    Subject Western Europe; Previous folder number: F-4c-16, Author:Vandenbosch, Amry
  - "The White Terror Finland", 1919 (Box 15, Folder 44)
    Subject Western Europe; Previous folder number: F-4c-17
  - "Oriental Affairs in the Light of the Kyoto Conference", 1929 (Box 15, Folder 45)
    Subject: Far East; Previous folder number: F-5-1, Author:Blakeslee, George H.; Foreign Policy Association no. 62
  - "Lord Cecil and Lord Parmoor on the Far East", 1933 (Box 15, Folder 46)
    Subject: Far East; Previous folder number: F-5-2, Author:Cecil, Edgar; v. 2 no. 16
  - "Tse Tsan Tai", 1917 (Box 15, Folder 47)
    Subject: Far East; Previous folder number: F-5-3, Author:Duncan, Chesney
  - "Freedom and Peace: with Korea Under Japan?", 1919 (Box 15, Folder 48)
    Subject: Far East; Previous folder number: F-5-4, Author:Korean Publication
  - "Address...Princeton University", 1917 (Box 15, Folder 49)
    Subject: Far East; Previous folder number: F-5-5, Author:Megata, Janetaro
  - "The Far Eastern Republic Siberia and Japan", 1922 (Box 15, Folder 50)
    Subject: Far East; Previous folder number: F-5-6, Author:Moore, Frederic F.; Skuirsky, Boris E. and Smith C.H.
  - "The Lena Case", 1930 (Box 15, Folder 51)
    Subject: Far East; Previous folder number: F-5-7, Author:The Times, London (England)
  - "American-Russian Relations in the Far East, 1914-1933", 1947 (Box 15, Folder 52)
    Subject: Far East; Previous folder number: F-5-8, Author:Tompkins, Pauline
  - "A Scheme of Indian States", 1924 (Box 15, Folder 53)
    Subject: India; Previous folder number: F-6-1, Author:Aiyar, V. Sundaram
  - "India", 1943 (Box 15, Folder 54)
    Subject: India; Previous folder number: F-6-2, Author:American Outpost in Great Britain
  - "Speech Delivered August 1, 1941" (Box 15, Folder 55)
    Subject: India; Previous folder number: F-6-3, Author:Amery, Leopold Charles
  - "A Plea for India's Freedom", 1930 (Box 15, Folder 56)
    Subject: India; Previous folder number: F-6-4, Author:Blaine, John J.
  - "Democracy for India", 1940 ca. (Box 15, Folder 57)
    Subject: India; Previous folder number: F-6-5, Author:Brailsford, H.N.
  - "British Survey-India", 1942 ca. (Box 15, Folder 58)
    Subject: India; Previous folder number: F-6-6, Author:British Association For International Understanding, The
  - "British Survey-India", 1939 (Box 15, Folder 59)
    Subject: India; Previous folder number: F-6-7, Author:British Association for International Understanding, The
  - "India", 1940 (Box 15, Folder 60)
    Subject: India; Previous folder number: F-6-8, Author:British Library of Information, The
  - "Choice Before India", 1943 ca. (Box 15, Folder 61)
    Subject: India; Previous folder number: F-6-9
  - "India and the World Crisis: Is Gandhi Pro-Axis?", 1948 ca. (Box 15, Folder 62)
    Subject: India; Previous folder number: F-6-10, Author:Das, Taraknath
  - "United India and World Peace", 1946 ca. (Box 15, Folder 63)
    Subject: India; Previous folder number: F-6-11, Author:Das, Taraknath
  - "India Financial Agreement Between the Government of the United Kingdom and the Government of India", 1947 (Box 15, Folder 64)
    Subject: India; Previous folder number: F-6-12, Author:Eady, Wilfred, Rao, Narahari V.
  - "To the Workers and Peasants of India", 1942 (Box 15, Folder 65)
    Subject: India; Previous folder number: F-6-13, Author:Fourth International
  - "Free India", 1930 (Box 15, Folder 66)
    Subject: India; Previous folder number: F-6-14
  - "India's Case before the White House", 1933 (Box 15, Folder 67)
    Subject: India; Previous folder number: F-6-15, Author:Gangulee, Mayadevi
  - "India", 1930 (Box 15, Folder 68)
    Subject: India; Previous folder number: F-6-16, Author:Ghose, Sailendranth
  - "India, 1939-1942" (Box 15, Folder 69)
    Subject: India; Previous folder number: F-6-17, Author:Harrison, Agatha and Baily Gerald
  - "The British Government in India", 1941 ca. (Box 15, Folder 70)
    Subject: India; Previous folder number: F-6-18, Author:Higgenbottom, Sam
  - "India's Charter of Freedom", 1947 ca. (Box 15, Folder 71)
    Subject: India; Previous folder number: F-6-19, Author:India, Constituent Assembly
  - "One Year of Independence", 1948 (Box 15, Folder 72)
    Subject: India; Previous folder number: F-6-20, Author:India, Embassy
  - "India", 1949 (Box 15, Folder 73)
    Subject: India; Previous folder number: F-6-21, Author:India, Embassy, USA
  - "Conversations Between the Governor General of India and Mr. Gandhi", 1931 (Box 15, Folder 74)
    Subject: India; Previous folder number: F-6-22, Author:India, Government of
  - "White Paper on Hyderabad", 1948 (Box 15, Folder 75)
    Subject: India; Previous folder number: F-6-23, Author:India, Government of
  - "Manifesto to the American People", 1930 ca. (Box 15, Folder 76)
    Subject: India; Previous folder number: F-6-24, Author:India Independence Central Committee
  - "Documents Regarding Kashmir", 1949 (Box 15, Folder 77)
    Subject: India; Previous folder number: F-6-25, Author:India Information Services, Government of
  - "Indian White Paper on Kashmir", 1948 (Box 15, Folder 78)
    Subject: India; Previous folder number: F-6-26, Author:India Information Services, Government
  - "New Government for Kashmir", 1948 (Box 15, Folder 79)
    Subject: India; Previous folder number: F-6-27, Author:India Information Service, Government of
  - "Simla Conference Correspondence", 1946 (Box 15, Folder 80)
    Subject: India; Previous folder number: F-6-28, Author:India Information Services, Government of
  - "Treatment of Indians in South Africa", 1949 ca. (Box 15, Folder 81)
    Subject: India; Previous folder number: F-6-29, Author:India Information Service, Government of
  - "Twelve Months of War in Kashmir", 1948 ca. (Box 15, Folder 82)
    Subject: India; Previous folder number: F-6-30, Author:India Information Service, Government of
  - "U. N. Commission for India and Pakistan", 1948 (Box 15, Folder 83)
    Subject: India; Previous folder number: F-6-31, Author:India Information Service, Government of
  - "Development of Common Ideals in the British Commonwealth", 1944 ca. (Box 15, Folder 84)
    Subject: India; Previous folder number: F-6-32, Author:Indian Institute of International Affairs
  - "India and Aviation", 1944 ca. (Box 15, Folder 85)
    Subject: India; Previous folder number: F-6-33, Author:Indian Institute of International Affairs
  - "India and the Gulf", 1944 ca. (Box 15, Folder 86)
    Subject: India; Previous folder number: F-6-34, Author:Indian Institute of International Affairs
  - "India's Trade and Commerce with Commonwealth Countries", 1944 ca. (Box 15, Folder 87)
    Subject: India; Previous folder number: F-6-35, Author:Indian Institute of International Affairs
  - "Indian Currency", 1944 ca. (Box 15, Folder 88)
    Subject: India; Previous folder number: F-6-36, Author:Indian Institute of International Affairs
  - "Indian Currency in Retrospect", 1944 ca. (Box 15, Folder 89)
    Subject: India; Previous folder number: F-6-37, Author:Indian Institute of International Affairs
  - "The Indian States", 1944 ca. (Box 15, Folder 90)
    Subject: India; Previous folder number: F-6-38, Author:Indian Institute of International Affairs
  - "Planned Economic Development for India", 1944 ca. (Box 15, Folder 91)
    Subject: India; Previous folder number: F-6-39, Author:Indian Institute of International Affairs
  - "Population Problems in South East Asia", 1944 ca. (Box 15, Folder 92)
    Subject: India; Previous folder number: F-6-40, Author:Indian Institute of International Affairs
  - "Problems of Indian Currency and Exchange", 1944 ca. (Box 15, Folder 93)
    Subject: India; Previous folder number: F-6-41, Author:Indian Institute of International Affairs
  - "The Status of Indians in the Empire", 1944 ca. (Box 15, Folder 94)
    Subject: India; Previous folder number: F-6-42, Author:Indian Institute of International Affairs
  - "Technical and Economic Co-operation", 1944 ca. (Box 15, Folder 95)